Guide to the Irving McNeil Ives papers, 1862-1958
Ives, Irving McNeil papers, 1862-1958
- SERIES I. CORRESPONDENCE and LEGISLATION
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 1728 Payne (I.M.I.) - I & F Commerce - Assist State and Territorial Maritime Academies or Colleges - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 10)
    merchant marine (educational assistance); Frederick G. Payne
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 1772 I.M.I. - LPW - Amend Labor-Management Relations Act '47 Clarify authority of States and Territories - 1957-1958 (Box 222, Folder 11)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. Thye (I.M.I.) - D. C. - Appt. Gov, Lt. Gov. Legis. Assembly and Delegate of D. C. to House of Representatives - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 12)
    District of Columbia (legislation)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 1853, 85th - 19-- (Box 222, Folder 13)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 1869 85th Congress - To Amend TVA Act of 1933 - 1957-1958 (Box 222, Folder 14)
    public works, Tennesee Valley Authority; National Association of Electric Companies
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 2023 Case, N. J. (I.M.I.) - J C - Amend Immig. And Nat. Act. To admit escapee fleeing from Communist dominated area - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 15)
    immigration laws (U. S.), refugees; Wm. P. Rogers
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 2082 Allott (I.M.I.) - C A F. - Simplify Authority Secy. Agric. Re loans to farmers and stockmen - 1957-1958 (Box 222, Folder 16)
    agricultural finance
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 2175 I.M.I. - LPW - Registration and reporting of employee welfare and pension plans - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 17)
    welfare (registration and reporting), employee benefits
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 2580 Hill (I.M.I., etc.) - LPW - Amend. Sec. 314 (c) Public Health Service Act - Grants-in-Aid for Public Health Train. - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 18)
    public health; Grayson Kirk (telegram), Georg. M. Rhodes
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 2603 I.M.I. (Javits) ?LPW - Appropriate funds for piers between 17th St. Gowanus Creek and Ft. Hamilton - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 19)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 2623 I.M.I. (Javits) Public Works - Provide an Official Residence for the Vice President - 85th - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 20)
    U. S. Vice-President (Official residence)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 2888 - 1957-1958 (Box 222, Folder 21)
    welfare, pension plans
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 2888 ?2 - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 22-23)
    employee benefits, welfare, pension plans; Gordon Allot; Blue Cross Association
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 2925 I.M.I. - LPW - Amend Nat. Labor Relations Act to require Secret ballot for voting in labor organization - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 24)
    labor (legislation), labor (voting procedures)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 2926 I.M.I. - LPW - Amend IMRA to prohibit payments to Labor organizations by agents of employers, etc - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 25)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 2927 I.M.I. - LPW - Amend Nat. Labor Relations Act - Make certain kinds of picketing unfair Labor Practices - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 26)
    labor (legislation), labor practices
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 2928 I.M.I. - LPW - Amend Sec. 9 (F) (g) NLRA - requires org. to file info with Secy of Labor - info to be made public - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 27)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 2930 I.M.I. (Javits, etc.) - J C - Est. Commission on Immigration and Naturalization - 85th - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 28)
    immigration (study)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 3163 Smith (I.M.I., etc.) - LPW - Improve Education System - overall - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 29)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 3167 Javits (I.M.I., etc.) - LPW - Narcotics Hospital in N. Y. S. - Ellis Island - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 30)
    narcotics (legislation), narcotics (treatment center), N. Y. S. (Ellis Island); Lister Hill; Dept. Bureau of Narcotics
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 3187 Hill (I.M.I., etc.) - LPW - Strengthen National Defense by encouraging scientific pursuit in schools - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 31)
    education (legislation), education (science); Lister Hill
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 3433 Javits (I.M.I., etc.) - LPW - Prohibit discrimination because of age by contractors for the govt. and D. C. - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 32)
    employment (discrimination)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 3486 Kennedy (I.M.I.) - LPW - Amend Sec. 41 Longshormen's and Harbor Workers Act - System of safety rules and reg. - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 33)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 3626 Smith (I.M.I., etc.) LPW - To establish teaching hospital at Howard University - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 34)
    hospital (Howard University); Department of HEW
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 3860 (I.M.I.) Labor & P. W. Committee To amend the Labor Management Relations Act of '47 - Service employees - [1958] (Box 222, Folder 35)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 3974 - I.M.I. - amendment - discrimination against race, religion, color, etc. - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 36-37)
    labor (discrimination practices)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 3974 Kennedy (I.M.I., etc.) - To amend Taft-Hartley Act - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 38)
    labor (legislation); Edwin B. Dovley
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 4212 Thurmond (I.M.I., etc.) - Amend War Orphan's Educational Assistance Act, re handicapped for vocational training - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 39)
    education (war orphans)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. 4213 Thurmond (I.M.I., etc.) - To afford vocational rehabilitation to certain veterans?handicap or disability - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 40)
    education (vocational rehabilitation), veterans affairs
  - [U. S. Senate] S. Res 17 - Proposed Amendments to Rule XXII of the Standing Rules of the Senate (relating to cloture) - 85th - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 41)
    U. S. Senate (standing rules)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. Res 49 - 85th Congress - Constitutional Rights - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 42)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. Res 54 - 85th Congress - Improving Federal Law Enforcement and Administration of Justice - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 43)
    federal law enforcement (U. S.)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. Res 81 - I.M.I. (Clark, etc.) ?F. R. - re self rule for Cyprus - 85th - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 44)
    foreign relations (Cyprus)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. Res 120 Javits (I.M.I.) - F R - re operation of Suez Canal and estab. of supplementary rules - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 45)
    foreign relations, trade routes
  - [U. S. Senate] S. Res 138 Sparkman (I.M.I., etc.) - B & C - Give small business fair share purchases and prime contracts by military services - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 46)
    business (govt. contracts)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. Res 294 - I.M.I. - 10th Anniversary of Israel greeting - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 47)
    Israel (10th anniversary)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. Res 304 Murray (I.M.I., etc).) - Com. on Govt. oper. re: Stockpiles of chromite ores, concentrates, manganese - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 48)
    raw materials, stockpiling
  - [U. S. Senate] S. Res 314 Javits (I.M.I.) - F R - Western Hemisphere Summit Conference - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 49)
    foreign relations; Organization of American States
  - [U. S. Senate] S. Res 318 Bennet I.M.I.) - R. C. - To establish committee to preserve U. S. S. historical document - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 50)
    U. S. Senate (rules & admin.)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. Res 340 Johnson I.M.I., etc.) - Re death of James H. McClellan - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 51)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. Res 357 Javits (I.M.I.) - F. R. - International Conf. consider refugee problems - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 52)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. J. Res 30 - I.M.I. - C A S - To establish a U. S. Academy of Nursing - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 53)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. J. Res 35 Murray (I.M.I., etc.) - Interior - observe Fiftieth Anniversary of First Conf. of State Governors - Nat. Resources U. S. - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 54)
    conservation (50th anniversary)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. J. Res 38 85th Congress - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 55)
    mortgage loans
  - [U. S. Senate] S. J. Res 53 I.M.I. (Javits) Interior and Insular - Provides for John Jay home as national historical site - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 56)
    historical sites (U. S.)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. J. Res 72 85th - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 57)
    Anglo-American financial agreement
  - [U. S. Senate] S. J. Res 94 Hill (I.M.I., etc.) - LPW - Fin. Reports to labor under Labor Relations Act be made available to public - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 58)
    labor (legislation), labor (finances)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. J. Res 95 - I.M.I. - F R - Agreement Between N. Y. and Canada continuing Buffalo & Fort Erie Public Bridge Authority - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 59)
    international relations; Edmund Radwan
  - [U. S. Senate] S. J. Res 107 Aiken (I.M.I., etc.) - Pub. Wks. Creation of a Lake Champlain Bridge Commission - 1957-1958 (Box 222, Folder 60)
    Elisha T. Barrett, Emanuel Celler
  - [U. S. Senate] S. J. Res 127 Javits (I.M.I.) - J C - Est. Commission Assist Celebrate 350th Ann. Exploration Hudson River - 1957-1958 (Box 222, Folder 61)
    Hudson-Champlain (celebration comm.)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. J. Res 154 I.M.I. (Javits, etc.) - F R International Aviation Show - Invite - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 62)
    international relations
  - [U. S. Senate] S. J. Res 158 Smith (I.M.I.) - J C - Compensate U. S. Citizens for property vested under Trading with the Enemy Act - 1957-1958 (Box 222, Folder 63)
    WW II (property compensation); Mel Eaton
  - [U. S. Senate] S. J. Res 160 Javits (I.M.I.) - J C - To request the President to proclaim March as Neighborhood House Month - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 64)
    settlement movement (legislation)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. J. Res 183 I.M.I. (Javits) - Comm. Interior and Insular A. H. - St. Ann's Churchyard designated as national historic site - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 65)
    national historic sites; Dept. of the Interior
  - [U. S. Senate] H. R. 13549 Amendments (Javits, I.M.I.) - to increase benefits of federal Old Age Survivors and Disability Ind. (Comm. on Finance) - 1958 (Box 222, Folder 66)
    public assistance (legislation)
  - [U. S. Senate] Bill analysis - 85th Congress - 1957 (Box 222, Folder 67)
    price discrimination, interstate commerce, transportation, pension plans
  - [U. S. Senate] H. R. 6574 - 86th Congress - to authorize certain construction at Military Installations - 1959 (Box 223, Folder 1)
    military construction authorization
  - [U. S. Senate] H. R. 8002 - 85th - 1957 (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - [U. S. Senate] H. R. 8755 - Policeman and Fireman covered under Social Security - 1957 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    social security, policeman and fireman (retirement benefits)
  - [U. S. Senate] Misc. Congressional legislation - 1949-1959 (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 2705 - For relief of John Kintzig - 83rd Congress - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 2948 - For the relief of Chaim Wold Weintraub? - 83rd Congress - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 2986 - For the relief of Argirius Tsamisis 83rd Congress - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 7)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 2996 and H. R. 1323 - For the relief of Sister Ramana Maria (Ramana E. Tombo) - 1954-1956 (Box 223, Folder 8)
    immigration and naturalization
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 3601 - For the relief of Myong Suk Kim - 83rd Congress - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 9)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] The Li Family - 83rd Congress - 1952-1953 (Box 223, Folder 10)
  - [U. S. Senate] Miscellaneous Private Bills - 83rd Congress - 1953 (Box 223, Folder 11)
    Wm. Langer
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 69 - Dr. Peter C. T. Kao (S. 2101 - 1951) - 1951-1953 (Box 223, Folder 12)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 352 - Relief of Joanna Maria Drucka-Podberezka - 83rd Congress - 1952-1954 (Box 223, Folder 13)
    immigration; Dutton S. Peterson
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 353 - Relief of J. L. Ming - 1952-1954 (Box 223, Folder 14)
    immigration; Arthur H. Dean
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 354 - Relief of Inger Larson Capehart - I.M.I. - 1952-1954 (Box 223, Folder 15)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 355 - Wanda Luceri Maria Depadora, et al - 1952-1954 (Box 223, Folder 16)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 591 - Samuel V. Goekjian - 83rd Congress - 1952-1954 (Box 223, Folder 17)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 842 - Relief of John Pitlayes - 83rd Congress - 1950-1954 (Box 223, Folder 18)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 1176 - Relief of Peter Hoskins - 83rd Congress - 1952-1954 (Box 223, Folder 19)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 1189 - For relief of Estate of Edward Grissinger - 83rd Congress - 1950-1954 (Box 223, Folder 20)
    patents
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 1701 - For relief of Paul Stanley Blow - 83rd Congress - 1953-1955 (Box 223, Folder 21)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 1865 - I.M.I. - Relief of Dimitrius Manolitsa - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 22)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] Lai, Yook Sue and Chew Pint (Stephen C. Y. Pan) - 1953-1955 (Box 223, Folder 23)
    immigration, Dr. Stephen Pan
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] 548 - S. Freidoun Jalayer - 82nd - 1949-1951 (Box 223, Folder 24)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 550 - Sadako Kawamura Lawton - 82nd - 1950-1951 (Box 223, Folder 25)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 648 ?Evald Ferdinand Kask - 82nd - 1950-1951 (Box 223, Folder 26)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 879 ?Luigi Podesta 82nd - 1949-1951 (Box 223, Folder 27)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 67 - Anastasia J. Tsamisis (Private Law 120) (S. 2377 - 82nd Congress) - 1951-1953 (Box 223, Folder 28)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 68 - Mrs. Rebecca Godschalk - 83rd - 1952-1954 (Box 223, Folder 29)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 566 - Relief of Kerupe Herant Liman, Mrs. Violet Liman and Hilda Annik Liman - 83rd Congress - 1952-1954 (Box 223, Folder 30)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 660 - Senator Chavez - For relief of Pierino F. Berta - 1953 (Box 223, Folder 31)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 843 - Relief of Rabbi Eugene Feigelstock - 83rd - 1952-1954 (Box 223, Folder 32)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 946 - Senator Martin - For relief of Lief and Alan Nicolaisen - 1953 (Box 223, Folder 33)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 1079 - For relief of Alexander Welner (Alexander Kauschus) - withdrawn - 83rd - 1952-1953 (Box 223, Folder 34)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 1212 - Senator Lehman - For relief of Dr. Alice Masaryk - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 35)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 1610 - Senator Hugh Butler - For relief of Louis H. Deaver - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 36)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 1632 - For relief of Robert Brown and Morna Doris Brown - 83rd - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 37)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 1717 - Senator Lehman - For relief of Charles J. Herzberg - See also H. R. 4746 - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 38)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 1762 - For relief of S. A. Healy Company - 83rd - 1950, 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 39)
    U. S. govt. (contracts)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 2345 - Relief of Yun Tai Miao and Chao Pei Tsang Miao - 83rd - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 40)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 2369 - For relief of Karl Ullstein - 83rd - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 41)
    immigration, naturalization
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 2879 - I.M.I. - For the relief of Helen, Peter and Prudence Newberry - 83rd - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 42)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 3062 - For relief of American Society Company of New York - 83rd - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 43)
    U. S. govt. (finance); Wm. Lenger
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 771 - Congressman Kearney - For relief of Ayako Kimura - Eligible for citizenship under P L 162 - 83rd - 1953 (Box 223, Folder 44)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 777 - Congressman Keating - For relief of Richard H. Backus - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 45)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 778 - Congressman Keating - For relief of Mrs. Jennie Maurello - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 46)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 783 - Congressman Keating - For relief of Theodore J. and Mrs. Eliza Hartung (mother) - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 47)
  - H. R. 803 - Congressman Kilburn - For relief of Christakis Modinus - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 48)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 804 - Congressman Kilburn - For relief of Enrichetta F. U. Meda-Novaro - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 49)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 806 - Congressman - For relief of Sullivan Construction Co. - 83rd - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 50)
    U. S. govt. (contracts - construction)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 917 - Congresswoman St. George - For relief of Luigi Lotto - 83rd - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 51)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 1495 - Congressman Radwan - For relief of Louis M. Jacobs - 83rd - 1953 (Box 223, Folder 52)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 1496 - Congressman Radwan - For relief of Mrs. Hermine Lamb - Private Law #230 - 83rd Congress - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 53)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 1697 - Congressman O'Brien - For the relief of Katharina Batke - 83rd - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 54)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 1772 - Congressman Latham - For the relief of Kenneth R. Kleinman - 83rd - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 55)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 1780 - Congressman Miller - For the relief of Edward F. Sheen - 83rd - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 56)
    veterans affairs; Wm. E. Miller, Eugene D. Milliken
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 1946 - Congressman Coudert - For relief of Capt. Hugo N. Solano - 83rd - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 57)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 2163 - Congressman Dorn - For relief of Lillian Schlossberg - 83rd - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 58)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 2774 - Congressman Buckley - For relief of Andrew Sendy - 83rd - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 59)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 3273 - Congressman O'Brien - For relief of Edgar A. Belleau - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 60)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 3276 - Congressman Reed - Relief of Mrs. Margaret D. Surhan - 83rd - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 61)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 3522 - Congressman Radwan - For relief of Arthur S. Rosithar - 83rd - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 62)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 3619 - Congressman Cole - For relief of Rufin Manikowski - Private Law 251 - 83rd Congress - 1953 (Box 223, Folder 63)
    immigration, Jack Calkins
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 3624 - Congressman Keating - For relief of Peter M. Leaming - 83rd - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 64)
    immigration; Kenneth Keating
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 3630 - Congressman Wainwright - For relief of Mrs. Nathalie Iliine - 19 (Box 223, Folder 65)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 3631 - Congressman Wainwright - For relief of Dorothy Sonya Goldschmidt - 83rd - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 66)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 3677 - Congressman O'Brien - For the relief of Sister Paolina - 83rd - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 67)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 3728 - Congressman Delaney - For relief of Helen Gertrude Bonanno (nee Koubak) - 83rd - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 68)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 3733 - Congressman Dorn - For relief of Mrs. Anna Holder - 83rd - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 69)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 3961 - Congressman Kearney - For relief of Margherita DiMio - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 70)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 3970 - Congressman Ray - For relief of Bernard Elmer - 83rd - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 71)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 4375 - Mr. Gamble - For relief of Julia S. Criswell - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 72)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 4474 - Congressman Keating - For relief of Frederick Joseph Buttacio and others - 83rd - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 73)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 4746 - Congressman Javits - For the relief of Chas. J. Herzberg - see also S. 1717 - 1953 (Box 223, Folder 74)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 5195 - Congressman Keating - For the relief of Max Kassner - Private Law #246 - 83rd Congress - 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 75)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 5461 - Congressman Derounian - For relief of Wah Chang Corp. - 83rd - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 76)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 5552 - Congressman Dean Taylor - For relief of John Hatzigeorgian (Hatgegeorge) - 83rd - 1953 (Box 223, Folder 77)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 5950 - Congressman Ray - For relief of Gattas E. Maloof - 1953 (Box 223, Folder 78)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 6967 - Congressman Albert H. Borch - For relief of Guerdon Plumbey - 83rd - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 79)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 7088 - Congressman O'Brien - For the relief of Antonia Cazzato - 83rd - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 80)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 7464 - Congressman Williams - For relief of Ellinor H. Anthony - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 81)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 7500 - Congressman Kearney - For relief of Kent Forsell - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 82)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 7559 - Congressman Cellar - For the relief of Madeleine Aquarone - 1954 (Box 223, Folder 83)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 7635 - Congressman Pillion - For relief of Martti Iimari Timmen, Maj-lis Timmen and Marja Timmen - 1954 (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 7931 - Congressman Gwinn - For relief of Gunther H. Halin - 1954 (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 8283 - Congressman Gamble - For relief of Vesmu and Gustav Fridenvalds - 1954 (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] H. R. 9750 - Congressman Dean Taylor - For relief of T. I. Luther - 1954 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] House Private Bills - Misc. - 1954 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] Senator Taft Private Bills - Miscellaneous Correspondence - 1953 (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 575 ?Meniak, Frida and Peysack Lemberger - Brooklyn - 1952-1953 (Box 225, Folder 7)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 576 ?Rabbi Ignatz Kovesi and wife - Brooklyn - 83rd - 1951-1953 (Box 224, Folder 8)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 578 ?Mozesz Aba Kamien - Brooklyn - 83rd - 1951-1954 (Box 224, Folder 9)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 581 - Gruman Kalman - Lakewood, N. J. - 83rd - 1952-1953 (Box 224, Folder 10)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 582 - Miklus Friedmann - New York City - 83rd - 1952-1954 (Box 224, Folder 11)
    immigration; Pat McCarren
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 583 - Rabbi Hendl Feldman and family - Brooklyn - 83rd - 1951-1953 (Box 224, Folder 12)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 649 - Joseph Rosenblum - Lakewood, N. J. - 83rd - 1953 (Box 224, Folder 13)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 650 - Rabbi Phillip Schonberger and family - Brooklyn - 83rd - 1951-1953 (Box 224, Folder 14)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 651 - Szyja Morgenstern - Brooklyn - Taft - 83rd - 1953 (Box 224, Folder 15)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 698 - Abaetal Szejnbejm - New York - 83rd - 1953 (Box 224, Folder 16)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 700 - Rabbi Joseph Weisz and family - Brooklyn - 83rd - 1952-1953 (Box 224, Folder 17)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 1513 - Erno Schischa - Brooklyn - Taft - 83rd - 1953 (Box 224, Folder 18)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 1832 - Osjasz, Hersh, Rysa, Margolit and Moshe Braksmajar - New York - Taft - 83rd - 1953-1954 (Box 224, Folder 19)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 2492 - Henryk Schwartz - Brooklyn - Taft - 83rd - 1953 (Box 224, Folder 20)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 31 - 1956 (Box 224, Folder 21)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 397 - I.M.I. - For the relief of Mr. William Wueras - 85th - 1st, 83rd - 1956-1957 (Box 224, Folder 22)
  - [U. S. Senate. Private Bills] S. 398 - Benjamin Wachtfogel - 85th - 1st, 83rd - 1956-1957 (Box 224, Folder 23)